yunjii.com 2015-12-19

# Privacy Policy | Yunjii Web Directory

Yunjii.com (the "Company") is committed to maintaining robust privacy protections for its users. Our Privacy Policy is designed to help you understand how we collect, use and safeguard the information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our Service.

For purposes of this Agreement, "Service" refers to the Company's service which can be accessed via our website at http://www.yunjii.com in which users can submit links and description text to third party websites. The terms "we," "us," and "our" refer to the Company. "You" refers to you, as a user of Service. By accepting our Privacy Policy and Terms of Service, you consent to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy.

## 1\. Information we collect

We collect "Non-Personal Information" and "Personal Information". Non-Personal Information includes information that cannot be used to personally identify you, such as anonymous usage data, general demographic information we may collect, referring/exit pages and URLs, platform types, preferences you submit and preferences that are generated based on the data you submit and number of clicks. Personal Information includes only your name and email, which you submit to us through the submission proccess.

### Information collected via Technology

To activate the Service you do not need to submit any Personal Information other than your name and email address. To use the Service thereafter, you do not need to submit further Personal Information. However, in an effort to improve the quality of the Service, we track information provided to us by your browser or by our software application when you view or use the Service, such as the website you came from (known as the "referring URL"), the type of browser you use, the device from which you connected to the Service, the time and date of access, and other information that does not personally identify you. We track this information using cookies, small text files which include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to a user's browser from our servers and are stored on the user's computer hard drive. Sending a cookie to a user's browser enables us to collect Non-Personal information about that user and keep a record of the user's preferences when utilizing our services, both on an individual and aggregate basis.

### Information you provide us by submitting links

In addition to the information provided automatically by your browser when you visit the Site, to become a subscriber to the Service you will need to provide your name and email address. By submitting links, you are authorizing us to collect, store and use your name and email address in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

## 2\. How we use and share information

### Personal Information

Except as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy, we do not sell, trade, rent or otherwise share for marketing purposes your Personal Information with third parties without your consent. We do share Personal Information with vendors who are performing services for the Company, such as the servers for our email communications who are provided access to user's email address for purposes of sending emails from us. Those vendors use your Personal Information only at our direction and in accordance with our Privacy Policy.

In general, the Personal Information you provide to us is used to help us communicate with you. For example, we use Personal Information to contact users in response to questions, solicit feedback from users, provide technical support, and inform users about promotional offers.

### Non-Personal Information

In general, we use Non-Personal Information to help us improve the Service and customize the user experience. We also aggregate Non-Personal Information in order to track trends and analyze use patterns on the Site. This Privacy Policy does not limit in any way our use or disclosure of Non-Personal Information and we reserve the right to use and disclose such Non-Personal Information to our partners, advertisers and other third parties at our discretion.

In the event we undergo a business transaction such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of our assets, your Personal Information may be among the assets transferred. You acknowledge and consent that such transfers may occur and are permitted by this Privacy Policy, and that any acquirer of our assets may continue to process your Personal Information as set forth in this Privacy Policy. If our information practices change at any time in the future, we will post the policy changes to the Site so that you may opt out of the new information practices. We suggest that you check the Site periodically if you are concerned about how your information is used.

## 3\. How we protect information

We implement security measures designed to protect your information from unauthorized access. We protect your information from potential security breaches by implementing certain technological security measures including encryption and firewall technology. However, these measures do not guarantee that your information will not be accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed by breach of such firewalls and secure server software. By using our Service, you acknowledge that you understand and agree to assume these risks.

## 4\. Links to other websites

As part of the Service, we provide links to other websites or applications. We are not responsible for the privacy practices employed by those websites or the information or content they contain. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by us through the Site and the Service. Therefore, this Privacy Policy does not apply to your use of a third party website accessed by selecting a link on our Site or via our Service. To the extent that you access or use the Service through or on another website or application, then the privacy policy of that other website or application will apply to your access or use of that site or application. We encourage our users to read the privacy statements of other websites before proceeding to use them.

## 5\. Changes to our privacy policy

The Company reserves the right to change this policy and our Terms of Service at any time.  You should periodically check the Site and this privacy page for updates.

## 6\. Contact us

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy or the practices of this Site, please contact us by using the contact form.

Last Updated: This Privacy Policy was last updated on 20.06.2015.
